[
 {
  "timeless": "true",
  "question": "Who replaced Mick Mars on guitar for Motley Crue in 2022?",
  "options": [
   "C.C. DeVille",
   "Carlos Cavazo",
   "John 5",
   "Warren DeMartini"
  ],
  "correct": "John 5"
 },
 {
  "timeless": "true",
  "question": "Who played guitar on Dio's first album, 'Holy Diver'?",
  "options": [
   "Adrian Vandenberg",
   "John Sykes",
   "Jake E. Lee",
   "Vivian Campbell"
  ],
  "correct": "Vivian Campbell"
 },
 {
  "timeless": "true",
  "question": "Which of the following is NOT a song by Slayer?",
  "options": [
   "Blood Red",
   "Death Spiral",
   "Hell Awaits",
   "Skeletons of Society"
  ],
  "correct": "Death Spiral"
 },
 {
  "timeless": "true",
  "question": "What is the country of origin for the band Temple Balls?",
  "options": [
   "Denmark",
   "Finaland",
   "Norway",
   "Sweden"
  ],
  "correct": "Sweden"
 },
 {
  "timeless": "true",
  "question": "What is the name of W.A.S.P.'s debut album?",
  "options": [
   "Inside The Electric Circus",
   "The Headless Children",
   "The Last Command",
   "W.A.S.P."
  ],
  "correct": "W.A.S.P."
 },
 {
  "timeless": "true",
  "question": "What year did Metallica release the album 'Kill 'Em All'?",
  "options": [
   "1982",
   "1983",
   "1984",
   "1985"
  ],
  "correct": "1983"
 },
 {
  "timeless": "false",
  "question": "Which band has Rudy Sarzo NOT been a part of?",
  "options": [
   "Dio",
   "Dokken",
   "Quiet Riot",
   "Whitesnake"
  ],
  "correct": "Dokken"
 },
 {
  "timeless": "true",
  "question": "Who played guitar on Ozzy Osbourne's live album 'Speak of the Devil'?",
  "options": [
   "Brad Gillis",
   "George Lynch",
   "Jake E. Lee"
   "Randy Rhoades",
  ],
  "correct": "Brad Gillis"
 },
 {
  "timeless": "false",
  "question": "What is the name of Saxon's vocalist?",
  "options": [
   "Biff Byford",
   "Gifford Flaxen",
   "Robbie Rocke",
   "Tally Urburson"
  ],
  "correct": "Biff Byford"
 },
 {
  "timeless": "true",
  "question": "Who was the original drummer for Bulletboys?",
  "options": [
   "Bobby Blotzer",
   "Jimmy D'Anda"
   "Mick Brown",
   "Pauli Henderson",
  ],
  "correct": "Jimmy D'Anda"
 }
]